BRANNON GRAY TATUM

1700 W Wesley Rd NW

Atlanta, GA, 30327

(404) 375-5821

graygrayt@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working Biology major (3.72 GPA) currently attending The University of Texas at Austin, with 5.5+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of lab experience, project management, and organizational skills to successfully fill the Lab/Research Intern role at your company. I look forward to fulfilling my passion for biology by achieving a genetics-focused career. Frequently praised as adaptable by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its specific goals.

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Austin Austin, TX

Bachelor of Science and Arts Biology Candidate (Expected graduation May 2021)

- **GPA:** 3.72
- Relevant Coursework: Cellular Biology, Microbiology, Genetics, Chemistry Lab, Biology Lab, Chemistry I & II, Evolution
- Awards & Honors: University Honors, Fall 2017, Spring 2018, Spring 2019
- Extracurricular Activities: Wooldridge Elementary School Reading Tutor, Garden Hills Elementary Tutor, Odyssey Academic Enrichment Program, Boys and Girls Club Volunteer, Sports Management, Kappa Kappa Gamma (ΚΚΓ)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Oxbow Real Estate, Atlanta, GA

Intern and Research Assistant, May 2019 – Aug 2019

- Create company magazine describing service offerings and industry news.
- Identify potential markets and customers for services.
- Initiate market research studies and analyze the findings.
- Coordinate promotional activities, working with advertisers to market products or services.
- Organize potential clients and current clients into spreadsheets containing relevant service information.

Watt's Jewelry, Atlanta, GA

Business & Creativity Assistant, May 2018 – Aug 2018

- Compute costs of labor and materials to determine production costs of products and articles.
- Examine finished products to ensure conformance to specifications.
- Design and create new jewelry and modify existing designs.
- Research and analyze reference materials, and consult with interested parties in order to develop new products and modify existing designs.

Gray Jewelry, Atlanta, GA

Company Owner, May 2012 - May 2017

- Design and create jewelry from materials, advertise products and manage client requests.
- Coordinate activities of business by holding trunk shows and managing finances.

• Analyze operations to evaluate the performance of the company to determine areas of potential cost reduction or improvement.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Spanish-Moderate Speaking and Writing Level
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Microsoft Excel
- R Studio-Basic Level
- Social Media Management

REFERENCES

References available upon request